<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> - Articles</title>
    <description>All things CS</description>
    <link>
    http://localhost:4000</link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Ghost</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey! Welcome to Ghost, it’s great to have you :)&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/welcome</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/welcome</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Managing Ghost users</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Ghost has a number of different user roles for your team&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;authors&quot;&gt;Authors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The base user level in Ghost is an author. Authors can write posts, edit their own posts, and publish their own posts. Authors are &lt;strong&gt;trusted&lt;/strong&gt; users. If you don't trust users to be allowed to publish their own posts, you shouldn't invite them to Ghost admin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;editors&quot;&gt;Editors&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Editors are the 2nd user level in Ghost. Editors can do everything that an Author can do, but they can also edit and publish the posts of others - as well as their own. Editors can also invite new authors to the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;administrators&quot;&gt;Administrators&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The top user level in Ghost is Administrator. Again, administrators can do everything that Authors and Editors can do, but they can also edit all site settings and data, not just content. Additionally, administrators have full access to invite, manage or remove any other user of the site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;theowner&quot;&gt;The Owner&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There is only ever one owner of a Ghost site. The owner is a special user which has all the same permissions as an Administrator, but with two exceptions: The Owner can never be deleted. And in some circumstances the owner will have access to additional special settings if applicable — for example, billing details, if using Ghost(Pro).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It's a good idea to ask all of your users to fill out their user profiles, including bio and social links. These will populate rich structured data for posts and generally create more opportunities for themes to fully populate their design.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 07:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/managing-users</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/managing-users</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Making your site private</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you might want to put your site behind closed doors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've got a publication that you don't want the world to see yet because it's not ready to launch, you can hide your Ghost site behind a simple shared pass-phrase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can toggle this preference on at the bottom of Ghost's General Settings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://casper.ghost.org/v1.0.0/images/private.png&quot; alt=&quot;private&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghost will give you a short, randomly generated pass-phrase which you can share with anyone who needs access to the site while you're working on it. While this setting is enabled, all search engine optimisation features will be switched off to help keep the site off the radar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do remember though, this is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; secure authentication. You shouldn't rely on this feature for protecting important private data. It's just a simple, shared pass-phrase for very basic privacy.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 06:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/private-sites</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/private-sites</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Setting up your own Ghost theme</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Creating a totally custom design for your publication&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghost comes with a beautiful default theme called Casper, which is designed to be a clean, readable publication layout and can be easily adapted for most purposes. However, Ghost can also be completely themed to suit your needs. Rather than just giving you a few basic settings which act as a poor proxy for code, we just let you write code.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a huge range of both free and premium pre-built themes which you can get from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://marketplace.ghost.org&quot;&gt;Ghost Theme Marketplace&lt;/a&gt;, or you can simply create your own from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://marketplace.ghost.org&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://casper.ghost.org/v1.0.0/images/marketplace.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;marketplace&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyone can write a completely custom Ghost theme, with just some solid knowledge of HTML and CSS&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghost themes are written with a templating language called handlebars, which has a bunch of dynamic helpers to insert your data into template files. Like &lt;code&gt;&lt;/code&gt;, for example, outputs the name of the current author.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The best way to learn how to write your own Ghost theme is to have a look at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/TryGhost/Casper&quot;&gt;the source code for Casper&lt;/a&gt;, which is heavily commented and should give you a sense of how everything fits together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;default.hbs&lt;/code&gt; is the main template file, all contexts will load inside this file unless specifically told to use a different template.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;post.hbs&lt;/code&gt; is the file used in the context of viewing a post.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;index.hbs&lt;/code&gt; is the file used in the context of viewing the home page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;and so on&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We've got &lt;a href=&quot;http://themes.ghost.org/docs/about&quot;&gt;full and extensive theme documentation&lt;/a&gt; which outlines every template file, context and helper that you can use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to chat with other people making Ghost themes to get any advice or help, there's also a &lt;strong&gt;#themes&lt;/strong&gt; channel in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://slack.ghost.org&quot;&gt;public Slack community&lt;/a&gt; which we always recommend joining!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/themes</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/themes</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Businessman &amp; The Fisherman</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;An American businessman took a vacation to a small coastal Mexican village on doctor’s orders. Unable to sleep after an urgent phone call from the office the first morning, he walked out to the pier to clear his head. A small boat with just one fisherman had docked, and inside the boat were several large yellowfin tuna. The American complimented the Mexican on the quality of his fish.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/the-businessman-and-fisherman</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-businessman-and-fisherman</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>A Full and Comprehensive Style Test</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2012 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/a-full-and-comprehensive-style-test</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/a-full-and-comprehensive-style-test</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>I Have a Dream</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I am happy to join with you today in what will go down in history as the greatest demonstration for freedom in the history of our nation.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 1963 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/i-have-a-dream</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/i-have-a-dream</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>The Purpose of Education</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;As I engage in the so-called “bull sessions” around and about the school, I too often find that most college men have a misconception of the purpose of education. Most of the “brethren” think that education should equip them with the proper instruments of exploitation so that they can forever trample over the masses. Still others think that education should furnish them with noble ends rather than means to an end.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 1948 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/the-purpose-of-education</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/the-purpose-of-education</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Out to Sea</title>
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;I had this story from one who had no business to tell it to me, or to any other. I may credit the seductive influence of an old vintage upon the narrator for the beginning of it, and my own skeptical incredulity during the days that followed for the balance of the strange tale.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 1912 10:18:00 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>
        http://localhost:4000/out-to-sea</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/out-to-sea</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
